what is up everyone my name will be Josh
this is strange central and today we are
going to be doing a product review on
the candy pens aura so the candy pens
aura is the latest version of the candy
pens earring or portable dab break
portable email rig whatever you want to
actually call these these kind of seem
to be like go-to thing in 2019 almost
every company has like released a
version of these or something kind of
similar to this and after kind of trying
all of them and going through all of
them this is my opinion actually is the
best one this was the like latest
released unit so I think they kind of
took their time to refine see kind of
what the problems are with the other
rigs and they released this beauty which
we're gonna get into today alrighty guys
so I got this thing actually heating up
getting ready to take a DAB here it does
have a five-second heat up so just click
the button two times and we're ready to
start taking our devs so I definitely
hope you guys are smoking along davin
long vaping long getting those
cannabinoids nice and deep into your
lungs because these are gonna be deep
into mine cheers friends I'm Davin today
on some banana sherbert
[Music]
actually my thing is things got more
ripping it
[Music]
success oh my goodness
so for portable rig getting a hit like
that on-the-go without actually carrying
around a torch and nail and a rig it's a
really really really really hard thing
to do you're not gonna get any kind of
hit like that off of any kind of a vape
pen but let's go ahead and jump directly
in the specs for this unit so we're
going to start off with the actual
battery this thing actually doesn't have
a 3000 milliamp hour battery in it and
it's actually charged with USB C which
is pretty unique I don't see very many
units that you actually have that USB C
charging new-age charging is almost what
we can call that and then moving on to
the actual like base and the battery I
do want to say this about the base and
the atomizer there is a lifetime
warranty on the actual products
obviously not a damage warranty like if
you break it it sits on you but if it's
defective if the product ever becomes
defective there is actually a lifetime
warranty on the battery and the atomizer
and that brings me into the actual
atomizer portion which I think honestly
is the coolest part of the unit so going
on to the actual atomizer this thing is
literally a game changer especially
after the peak disaster where atomizers
were breaking and breaking and breaking
and breaking and it's been said in some
places that that was actually almost
like the wholesale model for the peaks
was they wanted them in shops because
shops would be selling more atomizers
because the atomizers would break
eventually or actually quickly in most
cases so these guys have changed the
atomizer game on email units because
it's not an actual like replaceable
atomizer per se and though some people
will hear that and almost be like
off-put because they're like wait I
can't replace my atomizer so the way
that they built this unit is essentially
this there's a heating element in which
cups sit on and you can just screw the
cups directly in so the cups sit on top
of a already built-in atom
and like I've said several times there
is a lifetime warranty on that actual
atomizer when it comes to you know the
products so if that ever becomes
defective you are gonna be able to get
that replaced from the company and candy
pens has really good customer service
from all of my prior interactions also I
got to talk with the owner of this
product to Hempfest
and actually kind of relay all my
concerns and he listens very very
intently and like wanted to hear what
was wrong so it can be fixed and that's
something I look forward almost every
product that I buy is the company
actually wanting to innovate and wanting
to make the product better but going
back to the actual atomizer so there is
two actual cups included there's a
quartz and a ceramic cup and like I said
it takes literally five to ten seconds
to screw new cup in which means they can
be taken out and cleaned the quartz can
be soaked in ISO and actually here's a
quick pro tip when it comes to just
using the unit and getting the unit to
melt getting the unit to work better a
lot of people will say that you can
actually have two seasoned quartz which
means you have to kind of like either
put some oil in it heat it up get it
into use before it really starts kind of
like absorbing your oil and in diffusing
heat better so I've read on some FC
forums and I box I've tested myself and
it's worked really well that if you
actually take a torch and you kind of
like torch your quartz just a little bit
don't overdo it obviously and break your
bucket but if you season your quartz
yourself and then put it back in the
atomizer it actually does get ripping a
lot lot lot better and I'm not saying
put it back in the atomizer or hot I'm
saying heat up the quartz dish let it
sit let it cool down and put it back in
your atomizer and you're gonna have a
seasoned quartz dish so just even being
able to season a nail just so you can
get the unit more functional is
something that most you know pre-built
atomizers you're not going to be able to
do so I think for many many reasons
having an atomizer that's built around
buckets that can be replaced is so
ingenious because they can kind of keep
up with trends like let's say there's
some kind of new quartz or some kind of
new material that we're using in a year
they can make buckets out of those that
we just throw into those instead of
having to pre build a demise
around that specific material so for a
whole host of reasons I absolutely love
the candy pens actually did make this
kind of a prebuilt atomizer in which you
just replace and swap buckets for
because it just makes the entire thing
much much simpler and being able to sell
you a bucket is much cheaper on
everyone's ends than having to you know
buy an entire atomizer every time one of
them shits out all right so I'm just
come up one more DAB here really quickly
and we will talk about the pros and the
cons of this unit I think the last
couple of things that I haven't covered
yet is the fact that it's actually made
of a zinc alloy the casing is made of a
zinc alloy and then there is actually I
I don't know why I didn't mention this
probably because I just assumed you saw
it there is a glass top to this as well
but this is actually heated up and ready
to go so cheers guys I'll talk about the
glass top here in a second let's get it
[Music]
this thing is a killer immediate dad
sweats okay so as I was saying prior
this does actually have a glass top to
it and the glass top has some pretty
basic diffusion
there's simply two holes that are
directly in the back of the unit and I
was really confused by that for a while
I was like why would they only put two
holes and it's actually a question that
I have presented to the owner and was
like why is there not five holes why is
there not diffusion all the rounds I
feel like this could diffuse better and
you know really actually smart and very
quick answer to it so while you're
actually using the unit users tend to
tip the unit back and when you tip the
unit back these two holes that are
basically forced to be placed like this
because there's only one actual airflow
hole that you do that kind of place into
what attaches to the atomizer it
basically allows for the unit to
function better slightly tipped so what
will function just fine sitting straight
up and down but if you type it's like
kind of tip slightly back how most
people will be using the unit it's gonna
function best with the two holes of
diffusion
so they've product tested this they've
actually seen what works best and they
figured out the two holes is kind of
what they went with are you guys so
jumping in to the pros and the cons of
this unit I'm gonna be 100% honest I
have picked this thing apart
I have shredded this thing for weeks I
have tried to find every flaw in this
you
and I've honestly really only came up
with two and one of them is something
that the unit itself is actually
accounting for so the first one is the
highest temperature setting I personally
think the temperature setting I'm using
right now which I have kind of nicknamed
the cloud setting or the blue setting is
slightly too hot that being said there's
two things I have to say accompanying
that one some people like the high
temperatures and to the owners already
aware and and thinking about ways to
kind of like work around this so they're
aware of it and and it's something that
I have made known to him so hopefully
that's something we will see if there
ever is a v2 which that really doesn't
need to be as this thing is almost
perfect that is something that might be
adjusted but like I said there is some
people who do like the hotter dabs so
some people are gonna like that
temperature setting and then my second
technical con with the unit is there
will be occasional times where you will
kind of like accidentally bump it on and
turn it on as it is touch sensor but the
touch sensor is also leading me into my
first pro and that point also leads me
into my first pro unlike almost every
other unit or actually unlike every
other unit on the market these guys have
the wits about them to include something
so basic but so necessary an auto
shutoff feature you don't want to run
through your battery you don't want to
waste your battery so after I think five
minutes this thing will actually turn
off by itself to preserve your battery
and that's such a basic thing to peek
just entirely over mists and like it was
like a quick oversight that was really
really important it's almost like they
weren't using their product or something
other pros though I kind of covered most
of them already the huge thing for me is
the atomizer build and the fact that you
can quickly just replace those cups if
you really want to at literally any
point any time the next vote if you
heard that buzz right there that was the
unit actually Auto shutting off by
yourself the second one is going to be
battery life I think that kind of goes
back to that first point in the fact
that they were aware that the battery is
something that you want to try to
preserve that's why they included an
auto shutoff so with that 3000 milliamp
hour battery you are also gonna get
really really good battery life with the
unit and then the biggest biggest
biggest part other than all the things
I've mentioned is that lifetime warranty
on the battery and atomizers a lot of
companies aren't going to back their
product like that a lot of companies are
just gonna try to force you to buy as
many atomizers as possible I'm not gonna
name names but I've named their name
several times that all being said I am
super super super impressed with what
candy pens actually came out with I am
super super stoked to actually have one
of these in my hands and I'm sure you've
seen these all over [\h__\h] Instagram
and all over YouTube and koala Sasha all
the big influencers have been using them
lately
and that's that's not just because we
were given them SPR it's literally
because this I think is going to be the
next huge in like a rig EU knit portable
unit because it really took all the
aspects like I said of the other ones
and encompassed it into this so I am
going ahead that was just the scraps the
last tab so I'm gonna head and scoop out
one more get ooh there's a cat hair on
this data get off there I don't want any
cat trips today my friends but I
definitely hope every single one of you
is having yourself an absolutely
incredible one I definitely hope if you
guys are having a rough day that you can
push through it keep that head up and
remember that tomorrow brings a new day
tomorrow brings hopefully something
better for us all but uh cheers my
friends I love y'all let's get a big ol
dollop glob here
I'm switching to a load zip my lungs
need a break these drains in true
goddess Ling's rats stay positive stay
medicated